"Imperial Ballad"
small adult
Meng Meng is now imprisoned in the prison of the Ministry of Punishment
I'm afraid they'll abuse lynching
I beg you
Help
let me go meet her
The Holy One has ordered
No one is allowed to visit
Meng Meng, you are so pitiful
He obviously made a contribution
Still have to be imprisoned in prison
Not enough to eat
Not warm enough to wear
Still have to be tortured
No one can help you
-Okay -What should I do?
alright
Don't cry
I'll make arrangements
real?
Thank you Mr. Shen
Don't just fall in love with me
Make a promise or something
You think too much
Your conditions are not enough
I am the most elegant and talented man in Kyoto
I'm actually disgusted by you
Thank you anyway
another
Don't thank me
I do it for Zhili’s sake
I am coming…
Everything is put away
Let's go
They are all things my adults need to use.
The prison is humid, I'm afraid she won't be used to it
Yes, I was too anxious to go out
I actually forgot to prepare these.
I never thought there would be anyone who cares about Meng Meng as much as I do
Thank you
OK
Don't waste time
You go and visit Mr. Meng quickly.
I will immediately enter the palace to meet the saint
-go-ok
The Holy Spirit has good skills
You come
Your Majesty
your mood at the moment
Not suitable for fighting with Chen
Your Majesty…
Your Majesty
You can't do it because of Meng Tinghui's incident
Are you angry with us?
Sir, this is a weapon to escape from
This is a drug to defeat the enemy
I lead you to escape from the prison
It’s true that heroes think alike
That's what I meant too
Meng Meng, we can’t stand this anger anymore.
We are no longer worthy of this position
Anyway, I'm at Hakufu Tower in Kyoto
It hasn’t been renovated for a long time.
The investment is not too much
We sublet the shop and return to Shazhou
live comfortably
My brother arranged for us to come visit
You are discussing a prison robbery in front of me
Is this appropriate?
Based on the friendship between Mr. Xiao Shen and the Holy Emperor,
Naturally, I won't be implicated
Nonsense
Escape like this
I am afraid that even if I am innocent, I will become guilty.
Get rid of these drugs and swords
Take it all back
That's too much, Your Majesty.
Finally passed three yuan and became the head of the Chawenyuan
Just dismiss him if he says he is dismissed?
Locked up in this shabby cell
What golden words
One word and nine words
It doesn’t all depend on his mood
If I had been there
I'm going to give him a scolding
I scolded him thoroughly
my god
Fortunately you are not here
Otherwise, I would be here right now
Just you two
we come today
He advised Lord Meng to admit his mistake and apologize to the Holy One.
admit mistake and apologize
Absolutely impossible
I don't think she shows any remorse at all.
I expected that she would act extreme
Cruel means
But never thought about it
She actually made the decision without permission
Didn't even tell me
That's right
The Holy Spirit will only dismiss her from her official position
That's showing mercy.
In my opinion, at least thirty canes
Only then can she remember it in her heart
elder brother
My sister asked you to persuade her to make peace, she didn’t ask you to make her angry.
Mr. Meng was just impulsive.
No offense intended
She didn't mean it
Could it be that I deliberately made things difficult for her?
The civil and military forces of the Manchu Dynasty are at odds with my intentions.
I appointed her against all odds.
She doesn't know how to cherish it
I joined the officialdom to eliminate evil.
Protect the people
those in authority
If you only care about official career
There must be a lot of bones under your feet
So the safety of the people is in front of us
How can you ignore death?
in Kyoto
I saw again and again that the Huxiao Gang colluded with the officialdom
If I don't kill him soon
How can we intimidate authority?
That Holy One
I want a courteous minister who follows the rules
Why should I be appointed as the head of the Chawenyuan?
That's right
Meng Meng is right
I have always regarded the law as my ink
But this time I also support Mr. Meng
I hope Mr. Meng can regain control of the Procuratorate
And according to my understanding of the Holy Spirit,
He doesn’t really want to remove Mr. Meng
adult
Has the Holy One issued a decree?
not yet
When I was in the palace
She shows strength and weakness
Talk to me
There are many tricks and tricks for the sake of the position of the Inspectorate
I gave her a chance and appointed her to the Chawenyuan.
How could she not know how to advance or retreat?
That's right
I think she is just proud of being favored
The Holy Spirit entrusted her with an important task
How dare she contradict the Lord?
Acting so recklessly and out of control
Not suitable for serving as an official in the court at all
The Holy One should send her back to Shazhou
Never be hired from now on
She is not suitable, but you are?
I should serve as a collector
Naturally more convenient
Meng Tinghui is the director of the Procuratorate
I have thought about it carefully
I know best whether she is suitable or not.
Then the Holy One still imprisoned Lord Meng?
I understand
On the surface, the Holy Spirit was punishing Meng Tinghui
In fact, it was to give an explanation to Zuo Xiangguo and other court officials.
In order to protect Meng Tinghui, the Holy One
It's really a lot of painstaking work.
When did I say I would protect her?
No decree has been issued yet
Then Master Meng is still the head of the Procuratorate
Everything can still turn around
In addition to appeasing public anger
The Holy Spirit did all this
What else is the purpose?
Xuanhuang
Where did it go?
baby
Where have you flown to?
I haven't seen you all day
master
Have you seen Xuanhuang?
never seen
But there is a guest outside the door
Specially sent a delicious snack
He also said that you can tell at a glance
Don't you see I'm busy?
put things down
- Get out - this...
go
Then I'll go to the door and have a look
Look for it quickly
Really
Xuanhuang
my darling
Where did this fly?
Xuanhuang
My baby
Who did this?
My darling
my heart…
Zuo Xiangguo wants to see you, go
Zuo Xiangguo takes care of everything
Why do you want to see me, a prisoner?
Why do you talk so much nonsense?
Zuo Xiangguo wants to see you
Has his own intention
You must dare to abuse lynching
The Holy One has many eyes and ears
Will definitely know
Your Majesty?
Do you really think that today’s Holy Emperor
Do you still have time to take care of you, a prisoner?
Walk
don't touch me
I go by myself
Don't play tricks
Otherwise you will suffer a lot
Walk
I like the smell of dying people the most
Especially beauties
Who are you?
Meng Tinghui
What you say to others
I remember every word
Leader of the Tiger Roar Gang
I only regret not cutting Lu Er into pieces that day
Crushing bones and scattering ashes
But it doesn't matter
you are next
I want to see how a dead man can take revenge.
Lu Da, take action
gang leader
Lu Da
- I fell into the trap, withdraw - OK
Chase
Master Meng was frightened
The subordinates are under the orders of the Holy One
Secretly protecting Mr. Meng
Hosei Kamiguchi Satoru
Interrogation of Minister of Punishment Wan Kai
Wan Shangshu
Who committed this murder?
gang leader
Gang leader, wait a moment
No, no, no
I can't do it anymore
You go quickly
Stop talking nonsense and let’s go together
Went towards Changle Street
Chase me
Your Majesty
The leader of the Huxiao Gang is missing
The secret guard followed to Changle Street
I saw only his bloodstains but not his person
disappeared very quickly
Changle Street?
Did Wan Kai reveal anything?
When I first arrived in Wanfu,
Wan Kai was hit with a dagger
Dying
Before he died he left this
Since Wan Kai is concerned about the Huxiao Gang,
He's just a throwaway
So the collusion between the Huxiao Gang and officials from the DPRK and China
no ordinary
The Holy Spirit personally came to the prison of the Ministry of Punishment to pick up the civilians.
The grassroots were flattered
you suffered
Beginner's intention
Why suffer?
Are you blaming me?
Common people dare not
If you have such a plan next time
Please let me know in advance
The grassroots are afraid that the acting is not realistic enough
You don’t need to think of yourself as a commoner from now on
Capture the Tiger Roar Gang
Although there is some recklessness
However, the merits are offset by the faults
Special feature now
government reinstatement position
You are still the head of the Procuratorate
I thank you, Your Majesty, for your kindness.
There is indeed collusion between the leader of the Huxiao Gang and Wan Kai
But after this person fled to Changle Street
A stone sinks into the sea
As for Wan Kai
I just ordered his interrogation
He died suddenly at home
Only a note was left
Your Majesty
The Holy One used his ministers as bait
I know it well
I hereby promise to the Holy One
As long as I stay in the Procuratorate for one day
The Tiger Roar Gang Incident
Will definitely get to the bottom of it
But today
I'm tired
Please ask Your Majesty to go back and rest
The wound on your neck
I will ask the imperial doctor
Diagnose and treat you well
to avoid leaving scars
I will take you back to the palace today
Send you back again
Thank you, Your Majesty, for your concern
Don’t bother the imperial doctor anymore.
If it leaves scars
You can also always remind me
Reflect on yourself all the time
Beginner's intention
Huang Bo
Personally escort Mr. Meng back
Make sure to keep her safe
yes
I also asked the Holy Lord to allow Chen to go back alone.
The minister resigned
-Will she always hate me? -His Majesty
Mr. Meng has a strong character
Just confused for a moment
In the future, we will surely understand His Majesty’s painstaking efforts.
Hard work?
I'm afraid she'll think I'm cold and heartless.
Master Meng
Master Meng is here
Lord Meng is back
Master Meng, Master Meng is back
Master Meng
-Mr.Meng-Mr.Meng
We have been waiting for three days
you are finally back
This is great
- it's so good - it's so good
Master Meng
Your injury?
Yes
I accidentally scratched it myself
As long as you are safe and sound
these days
Are the Tiger Roar Gang still causing trouble for you?
-no-no
Thanks to Master Meng
The land previously taken over by the Huxiao Gang
Now taken over by the government
Neighborhood
They also reburied the bones of their family members
Thank you, Mr. Meng
Help us seek justice
-Yeah yeah
if it weren't for us
You won't suffer such grievances either
-Thank you, Mr. Meng. -Thank you, Mr. Meng.
Get up quickly, Ah Cheng
Get up quickly
Get up, all get up
You don't have to do this
These are all my duties
As long as you're safe and sound
Master Meng
This is a little bit of our thoughts
Just accept it
You must accept it
Take it back quickly
this is what i should do
-Take them all back- Sir, those bullies
Drive our whole family out
Let us become refugees, homeless
If it weren't for your lord, you would take action
How can we go home?
-Yeah yeah
This is the fruit I personally picked from the mountain
Please accept it, sir.
Master Meng
I heard you are from Shazhou
This is Shazhou cuisine cooked by me
you are too thin
Eat more
Yes, Master Meng
-Master Meng-get up
My daughter has been missing for more than half a month
The Yamen said there were too many cases and they had no time to take care of them.
You must help me
Master Meng
Even ordinary people have great grievances
Master Meng, please make the decision for me.
Don't worry
The grievances of each of you
The Procuratorate will definitely seek justice for you
But these things
I really can't accept it
These are all things you have worked hard to save.
It’s just enough to maintain your livelihood
But the thoughts of each of you
I understand
thank you
Master Meng
it's us thank you
Now everyone knows
You and the Procuratorate
He sincerely works for the people
You are our backer
Not only will you protect us in the future
We all need to protect you more
Please accept these things.
Mr. Meng, take it.
I really can't accept it
thank you
Really can't accept it
Take it back
You accept it
I have given three orders to apprehend the Huxiao Gang.
But to this day there is still no news
Is this because they have great powers?
Or is someone secretly causing trouble?
The old minister is well aware of His Majesty’s worries
Now Wan Kai died suddenly
The Ministry of Punishment has no one in charge
Veteran minister recommends Minister of War
Temporary Ministry of Punishment
Thoroughly investigate the Huxiao Gang case
The case of the Tiger Roar Gang
I have given full authority to the Procuratorate for disposal
As for the candidates for the Ministry of Punishment,
I also have my own holy judgment
Your Majesty
Lao Chen wants to know
Who does the Holy Spirit wish to recommend?
Zuo Xiangguo might as well talk about it first
Why did Wan Kai follow your orders?
Mention Meng Tinghui privately
-Why did he die so suddenly in the house? -His Majesty
The old minister is willing to guarantee it with his head
What Wan Kai did
The old minister has no idea
It’s definitely not an old minister’s order.
Lao Chen and Meng Tinghui
It's political differences
But there is no intention to do any harm
Please give me a clear warning
Zuo Xiangguo said this lightly.
Wan Kai is about to burst into tears
You don't know anything
It's like your vicious dog biting someone outside.
The master can say that he is completely innocent
presumptuous
I discuss matters with the Holy Father
How can I allow you to make jokes?
I'm just telling the truth
If you are really innocent
Why are you afraid of these few jokes I said?
Shen Zhishu
Don't be rude to the left prime minister
Just now
The Ministry of War resells ordnance
Fraud in the Ministry of Etiquette Examination
Even the Minister of Punishment colluded with gangs
Harm the common people
Zuo Xiangguo, you have led the six ministries for many years.
A word of ignorance
I'm afraid it will be difficult to disentangle the relationship.
Minister dereliction of duty
minister…
Willing to resign from office
Retire old age and return home
Your Majesty
Zuo Xiangguo was entrusted by the late emperor
Assisted the Holy Father for more than ten years
Constant cold and heat
Although he is now over seventy years old
The memorials are still reviewed every day at Yin time
Come to the court at Mao hour to discuss matters
May the Holy Spirit remember old love
lighter punishment
Your Majesty
Legal principles are nothing more than human feelings
If Zuo Xiangguo is severely punished
The fear has chilled the hearts of the veterans.
What a great move to turn retreat into advance
Zuo Xiangguo is forcing the Holy Emperor
Making a choice between legal principles and human feelings
Zuo Xiangguo
But my Daning’s achievements in three dynasties
Pillar of the country
Hard work pays off
How can I really take responsibility for it?
It’s just that Zuo Xiangguo is old now
These six memorials, affairs of the world
I shall do it myself
Don’t bother Xiangguo Zuo...
You worked hard for me
Thank you, Your Majesty
good
Bo Feng Building opens today
Dear guests, please come inside
-Inside please -Inside please
Come, guest officer, please come inside
Watch out for steps
What kind of shabby restaurant?
Why on the first day of opening?
Steal half of my business?
The shopkeeper’s…
Shopkeeper, I heard about it
The owner of Bo Feng Building
She is Yan Fuzhi, the sworn sister of Lord Meng of the Inspectorate of Justice.
They had previously
Have you ever stayed in our hotel?
It turned out to be the two of them
It looks like collusion between government and businessmen
Climb into a relationship household
Junko
You should pay more attention on weekdays
See if I don’t catch their pigtails
Shopkeeper Yan, please stay.
Dear gentlemen
This is my Bofenglou’s unique Shazhou preserves
Eating it with apricot peel tea is the best way to relieve tiredness.
I hope the young master will accept it
Shopkeeper Yan is so considerate
I will definitely come to Bofeng Tower every day
Try this Shazhou delicacy all over
That's naturally the best
-Farewell-You walk slowly
Shopkeeper Yan, please wipe your saliva.
Everyone is gone
small adult
Which girl did you invite today?
Holy…
Shopkeeper Yan
wake up
This is a bit exaggerated, right?
If I don’t wake up, I’m going to die
You think beautifully
I heard that shopkeeper Yan Bo Feng Building is opening today
I brought my cousin to support me
Shopkeeper Yan doesn’t need to be polite
Just call me Hedu, where is she?
Meng Meng is upstairs. Mr. He, please come over here.
Watch out for steps
Shopkeeper Yan
How can we, both diners, favor one over the other?
Shopkeeper Yan’s handiwork
It's like a desert style
Moved to Kyoto
It can be said that there are views everywhere
There is no such thing as a cave
interesting interesting
On Changle Street
Nothing special
How to retain distinguished guests?
Except for the Wangyou Pavilion I left specially for Meng Meng
Other private rooms
All are single expenses for entertainment
Distinguished guests of more than one hundred taels
I believe that with Mr. Xiao Shen’s strength,
Soon you will have a room of your own
Meng Meng
Your Majesty
This white-faced man
Wherever did you go? Where did you take it?
Your Majesty
Yin Qing is a colleague of Chencha Wenyuan
Not some white-faced guy
The minister is handling the case
Yin Qing naturally wants to follow him
adult
The Holy One said that I am a white-faced man
Are you complimenting me?
Handling a case?
Are you handling the case here?
Leader of the Tiger Roar Gang
Finally disappeared in Changle Street
If I were to search with great fanfare,
I'm afraid it might scare someone off.
Pok Fung House is located on Cheung Lok Street, which is convenient for monitoring.
I have given this wing room
As an important base for collecting clues
Your Majesty
Anen
Today is in a hurry
It turned out to be a gift to our family.
Here comes the handyman in front of and behind the saddle
Where is the handyman?
Ah Nian, this is helping me handle official duties.
Your Majesty
Mr. Meng has been worried before
Investigate the Huxiao Gang
This is the portrait I painted based on her description
Although I only have a pair of eyes as a clue
But we will also follow Mr. Meng’s arrangements
Conduct a comprehensive investigation of Changle Street
I have been familiar with official families since I was a child
So I'm in charge of Changle Street
All high-end tea shops and drug stores
Yin Qing is good at dealing with women
So he is responsible
All rouge and gouache shops
There is also a brothel in Lefang
As for Lord Meng
She told me about her
Since childhood, I have been involved in three religions and nine schools of thought
So I'm responsible for all the gambling houses on this street.
There are also banks
Your Majesty
These arrangements of the Procuratorate
Is it also necessary to report it to the Holy One?
Waiting for the Holy Judgment?
That's not necessary
The Holy One suddenly arrived
Any advice?
Death of Wan Kai
I watched Xu Ting look magnanimous
The words are passionate, not like pretending
This note left by Wan Kai
The direction is still unknown
So after this
In addition to thoroughly investigating the Huxiao Gang,
Be sure to find out who is behind it
I will spare no effort
Investigate thoroughly
This is the secret medicine specially prepared by the royal doctor
Great for removing scars
It was specially given to Mr. Meng by the Holy One.
I thank you, Your Majesty, for your kindness.
But I have already used Yin Qing’s scar removal cream.
The injury has improved
Your Majesty, Lord Meng is healed
-No need.-Your Majesty
What Mr. Meng means is
If two medicines
mix together
will conflict
you mean…
Is your medicine more effective than mine?
No…
Thank you so much, Ron
No more business talk
In fact, Mr. He came today
Just to have a bite of authentic mutton noodles
Meng Meng
You've been learning to make mutton noodles in the kitchen these days
It turns out it’s for Mr. He.
Mr. He
Authentic mutton noodles coming soon
I…
-Where do I have it? -Walk quickly
I made an appointment with the teacher to learn painting skills
By the way, I will handle the official business assigned by Mr. Meng.
I won’t interrupt you to enjoy your drink.
There is only the Right Prime Minister
I can make you abandon me and Anian
Sister Zhili, I’ll give it to you
Only Zhili
I can make you leave me behind
Your Majesty
small adult
I remember
Mr. Meng also has some official business for me to handle.
I'm leaving first
It’s still easy to use the Holy Spirit
Why is this person gone?
Meng Meng
You said Mr. He came to Bo Feng Tower in person?
Also ordered mutton noodles
Does he feel that he punished you wrongly before?
Want to find a chance
Want to ease the relationship with you?
The king's heart is unpredictable
Don't make assumptions
Don't be too sentimental
Yes, he is the Holy One after all
You must not contradict him again
Otherwise, our few lives won’t be enough to compensate.
I didn't contradict him
Not contradicting, not contradicting
Meng Meng, look
You'll say it soon
This bowl of mutton noodles was made by you
So delicious
This is bullying
What should we do?
Yan Fuzhi…
Listen to me
You sprinkled this green onion
It’s equivalent to this bowl of mutton noodles
That's what you did
I'm just helping you out
This is no longer deceiving you.
Meng Meng
Meng…
Meng Meng, you are crazy
alright
This is what I did
The bowl of mutton noodles that my cousin ordered last time
Do I remember it?
Co-author Today is here to collect debts
How about it?
I have this arrangement today
Is my cousin still satisfied?
Is this a bit too extravagant?
Don't worry, cousin
You don’t have to spend money today
Shopkeeper Yan is the host
The co-authorship is blamed on Miss Yan.
Play with borrowing flowers to offer to Buddha
My cousin's words are wrong.
What about me?
I have prepared a big surprise for you
Master Situ has arrived
Coming
Mr. Shen and Mr. He
Thank you for inviting me
Nice to meet you
Mr. Situ Fang, nice to meet you.
It turns out this is
The surprise prepared by Mr. Shen
Mr. He
The mutton noodles made by Meng Meng are here.
Come…
Use slowly
Mr. He
-Please use it slowly-Everyone is here
Mr. Meng, Shopkeeper Yan
Let me introduce it to you
This is the legendary...
-Situ Xue-Situ Xue
Master Meng also knows Master Situ, right?
I heard Mr. He mention it
long admired name
Mr. Meng is overly praised
I have long heard about Mr. Meng’s reputation
See you today
feel honored
today
But my cousin specially invited Master Situ to come
Adding color to the opening of Bo Feng Building
Thank you Mr. He
this…
He must be the shopkeeper Yan from Bofeng Tower, right?
Yes, exactly down there
I have ordered the painting manager to arrange the musicians
Play for fun
-Congratulations on the opening of Bo Feng Building - first meeting
Prepare a small gift of gold unicorn
I wish shopkeeper Yan a prosperous financial life
Master Situ Fang comes to Bofeng Tower
Already full of brilliance
What other gifts are you bringing?
To attract wealth, collect it quickly
Everyone, please stop standing
Try Bo Feng Lou’s signature dishes
Unexpectedly, Hakufu Tower opened in Kyoto
-It turned out to be real-Situ Fangzhu, try it now
You should rarely socialize on weekdays
Thanks to my cousin today
Warm hospitality is…
It's okay, it's okay
Everyone, eat and drink quickly
Cousin has always been spicy and not happy
What happened today?
Mr. He
Warm the soup into the stomach
Is this mutton soup delicious?
delicious
Very delicious
This mutton noodles is still the same as the one in Shazhou.
Hot enough, cruel enough
If it tastes good, drink more
Mr. He in Shazhou
But I can eat two whole bowls
Mr. He, drink sea buckthorn honey quickly.
The best way to relieve spicy food
Ms. Meng’s warm hospitality
That leaves me with nothing to repay.
Mr. He is joking
Compared to Mr. He
I specially invited Master Situ here with all my heart.
What does my bowl of noodles mean?
Master Situ and I
Only a few acquaintances
Today, Master Situ comes to see you
It surprised me
Shopkeeper Yan and I do business together on Changle Street
I have long admired Master Meng’s reputation
Already ready to get acquainted
I am happy to attend the appointment
take this opportunity
I'd like to toast you all
I didn’t expect you to be the king of a country
To be so vindictive
You deliberately brought Situ Xue to mock me
Implement imitation in Shazhou East
It’s really hard to argue
I was harmed by you
It seems that between them
The relationship between king and minister is not as simple as that
I thought you could be reliable for once
I really can’t do anything
Good wine and delicious food, beautiful lady by your side
We must have a good drink today
It’s really rare to get together today
But I still have official duties to attend to
Excuse me now
Meng Meng, are you okay?
-I'll accompany you-No need
It’s rare for Master Situ to come
Please stay with me and have a few more drinks
Then eat, then drink
I also have something important to do
You eat first
cousin…
Shopkeeper Yan, Mr. Shen
I also have some urgent matters to deal with.
I'm leaving first
Such a good roasted Sanbai
Why are everyone gone?
Shopkeeper Yan, let’s drink
etc.
like…
It seems like this special wine
Not on it yet?
small adult
I'll get it for you right away
Drink...drink to death, forget it
small adult
Special wine is here
drink more
Don't drink and throw up
Dry
Sir, please go slowly
This way
Nine out of ten gambling
Ten gambles and nine cheats
I don't believe that the Tiger Roar Gang can really be exempted.
stop
Idle people stop
Why can't I go up to the second floor?
Sir, please forgive me.
This is the rule of Xingrong Casino
Won ten thousand taels
Only then can you go to the second floor
Who are you?
I am Zhuang He Agui
You look a little strange
Is this your first time visiting our casino?
We have a wedding ceremony here
Give away twelve lottery tickets
Your boss is quite good at doing business.
on the rivers and lakes
He's also a well-known figure, right?
A girl's discerning eye
Our boss’s surname is Hao
All the brothers on the road respectfully call him Uncle Hao.
Uncle Hao?
good
Then I will try my luck today
please
Girl, please wait a moment
I'm going to help you put together a game
Third Master…
New customers entering the market
Do you want to come and support me?
Why are you betting on a woman?
another…
Uncle Wang
Come and join us for a round
Female husband?
-If you don’t play, don’t play. -Don’t…
I'll bet with you
Sir, please have a seat, please have a seat.
Mr. He is really in high spirits today.
I just saw no one to bet with you
reluctantly
Play a game with you
That being the case
Let's get started